[
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "HTML contains?",
        "choices": [
            "<p> tags",
            "<s> tags",
            "<d> tags",
            "<t> tags"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "<p> tags"
    
    },
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "HTML contains?",
        "choices": [
            "<p> tags",
            "<s> tags",
            "<d> tags",
            "<t> tags"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "<p> tags"
    },
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "In HTML all?",
        "choices": [
            "tags must always have an opening and closing tag",
            "blocks must always have an opening and closing tag",
            "elements are represented by tags",
            "elements are written in UPPERCASE"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "elements are represented by tags" 
    },
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "HTML?",
        "choices": [
            "consists of elements used to structure a web pages",
            "uses rules to style a web page",
            "is a programming language",
         "can be used insead of JavaScript"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "consists of elements used to structure a web pages"    
    },
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "HTML elements?",
        "choices": [
            "are represented by tags",
            "change the size of the font",
            "are used to contain functions",
           "are always written in UPPERCASE"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "are represented by tags"

    
    },
    {
        "category": "HTML",
        "question": "HTML always have?",
        "choices": [
            "a head and a body",
            "5 sections",
            "4 sections",
           "an <end> tag"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a head and a body"   
    },


    {
        "category": "CSS",
        "question": "Cascading Style Sheets?",
        "choices": [
            "are used to remove styling format from html",
            "are used to write programming code",
            "contain a head and a body",
            "start with !DOCTYPE"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "are used to remove styling format from html"
    },
    {
        "category": "CSS",
        "question": "CSS is?",
        "choices": [
            "works with HTML to provide styling",
            "is another form of HTML",
            "is the same as HTML",
            "is part of the HTML page"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "works with HTML to provide styling"
    },
    {
        "category": "CSS",
        "question": "An example of CSS is?",
        "choices": [
            "background-color: red;",
            "<p></p>",
            "<img src=''>",
            "if/else statement"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "background-color: red;"
    },


    {
        "category": "JavaScript",
         "question": "JavaScript?",
        "choices": [
            "allows a user to make web pages more interactive",
            "is used to style a web page",
            "is the same as Java",
            "is also known as MERN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "allows a user to make web pages more interactive"
    },
    {
        "category": "JavaScript",
         "question": "JavaScript?",
        "choices": [
            "includes switch statements, loops and functions",
            "is used to change the style of a web page",
            "can only be used with REACT",
            "is a markup language"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "includes switch statements, loops and functions"       
    },
    {
        "category": "JavaScript",
         "question": "A method is?",
        "choices": [
            "an action that can be performed on an object",
            "not part of JavaScript",
            "is part of REACT",
            "is part of a switch statement"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "an action that can be performed on an object"

    },


    {
        "category": "React",
         "question": "React is?",
        "choices": [
            "both front end and back end framework",
            "only a front end framework",
            "only a back end framework",
            "neither front end of back end framework"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "both front end and back end framework"       
    },
    {
        "category": "React",
         "question": "React?",
        "choices": [
            "makes reusable bits of code",
            "uses methods as an action",
            "includes loops and functions",
            "only works in the cloud"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "makes reusable bits of code"

      
    },
    {
        "category": "React",
         "question": "React?",
        "choices": [
            "is a JavaScript library or building user interfaces",
            "includes switch statements, loops and functions",
            "is used to point to the HTML element you want to style",
            "Must always be part of the body"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "is a JavaScript library or building user interfaces"
    }
]

